<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>NotePage Software News - SMS and Paging Software News</title>
        <description>News relating to SMS messaging, text messaging and paging software.</description>
        <link>http://www.notepage.net/press.htm</link>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2011 15:46:17 -0400</lastBuildDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 1 Apr 2011 09:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <webMaster>webmaster@notepage.net</webMaster>
        <generator>FeedForAll v2.0 (2.0.1.0) http://www.feedforall.com</generator>
        <image>
            <url>http://www.notepage.net/notepage-logo-tweak.gif</url>
            <title>NotePage Press Releases</title>
            <link>http://www.notepage.net/software.htm</link>
            <description>press and announcements related to NotePage&apos;s software</description>
            <width>134</width>
            <height>138</height>
        </image>
        <item>
            <title>Latest SMS News from NotePage</title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[Hi , <br />
Welcome to NotePage news. If preferred this newsletter can also be viewed online at: <a href="newsletter-03-30-11.htm">http://www.notepage.net/newsletter-03-30-11.htm</a><br />
<b></b><br />
<b>PageGate</b><br />
The latest release version of PageGate is 5.0.93, make sure you have the current release. <br />
<br />
<b>PRTG Integration </b><br />
How Can I send SMS Text Messages in PRTG? This documentation from Paessler explains how to use NotePage's software with PRTG. <a href="http://www.paessler.com/knowledgebase/en/topic/393-how-can-i-send-sms-text-message-notifications-via-a-modem-or-a-mobile-phone-with-prtg" target="_blank" >http://www.paessler.com/knowledgebase/en/topic/393-how-can-i-send-sms-text-message-notifications-via-a-modem-or-a-mobile-phone-with-prtg </a><br />
<br />
<b>Orion Integration</b><br />
Are you using Solar Winds Orion in conjunction wih NotePage's software? This forum post will walk you through the setup.<br />
<a href="http://www.notepage.net/forum/viewtopic.php?p=11942">http://www.notepage.net/forum/viewtopic.php?p=11942 </a><br />
<br />
<b>PageGate Custom Training Webinars</b><br />
Interested in one on one training for PageGate? Customized webinars are available for training staff $100.00 for .5 hour webinar or $150.00 for a 1.0 hour webinar. You can ask questions, have us train your staff, this is your opportunity to get training on the specific items you want. If you prefer customized training email <a href="mailto:webinar@notepage.com">webinar@notepage.com</a> with contact details and we'll schedule your training session. <br />
<br />
<b>Group Webinar</b><br />
 Sign-up for FREE PageGate webinars. Not interested in personalized training? Join one of our group training webinars, here is the schedule:<br />
<br />
<b> Session 1 - April 27, 2011 at 12:00 EST Why would I need to send SMS?</b><br />
 In this session, we'll go over the different reasons that SMS can add extra efficiency to almost any business model and provide examples of different implementations of SMS messaging with a healthy amount of time for Q&A at the end of the session. <br />
<br />
Sign-up for session 1 by emailing <a href="mailto:webinar@notepage.com">webinar@notepage.com</a> with the name/date of the webinar.<br />
<br />
<b> Session 2: - May 11, 2011 at 12:00 EST What is PageGate?</b><br />
 In this session, we'll be going over the basics of how to use PageGate. We will cover how to install PageGate and configure it to send a basic page to a cel phone, pager, or email address.<br />
<br />
 Sign-up for session 2 by emailing <a href="mailto:webinar@notepage.com">webinar@notepage.com</a> with the name/date of the webinar. <br />
<br />
<b>Session 3: - May 25, 2011 at 12:00 EST What are the PageGate Interfaces? </b><br />
In this session, we'll be doing an overview of what each of the different Interfaces for PageGate are and covering the basics of how they work. This session will provide key information on how PageGate can seamlessly integrate with other applications and alarm systems.<br />
<br />
 Sign-up for session 3 by emailing <a href="mailto:webinar@notepage.com">webinar@notepage.com</a> with the name/date of the webinar. <br />
<br />
<b>Session 4: - June 8, 2011 at 12:00 EST PageGate Q&A </b><br />
Now that we've covered a lot of basic information, this session will be dedicated entirely to the questions you've submitted. This will be a freeform session where you, the participant, can guide the discussion.<br />
<br />
 Sign-up for session 4 by emailing <a href="mailto:webinar@notepage.com">webinar@notepage.com</a> with the name/date of the webinar.<br />
 Additional details on <a href="pagegate-webinar-schedule.htm">free PageGate Webinars</a>! <br />
<br />
<br />
<b>SMS Education Center </b><br />
Are you an independent learner? You can find SMS tips and tricks in the NotePage learning center.<br />
<a href="http://www.notepage.net/learning-center/notepage-learning-center.htm">http://www.notepage.net/learning-center/notepage-learning-center.htm</a><br />
<br />
<b>Green Tips</b><br />
Shut down, every night, at the end of the day shut computers down to conserve additional energy. <br />
<br />
<b>Check out our Green Links:</b><br />
Green Business Tips - <a href="http://www.notepage.net/green/green-business-tips.htm">http://www.notepage.net/green/green-business-tips.htm</a><br />
 Steps to Make Your Business Green - <a href="http://www.notepage.net/steps-businesses-can-take-to-go-green.htm">http://www.notepage.net/steps-businesses-can-take-to-go-green.htm</a><br />
NotePage is a Green Company - <a href="http://www.notepage.net/green/notepage-green-company.htm">http://www.notepage.net/green/notepage-green-company.htm</a><br />
 NotePage's Green Efforts - <a href="http://www.notepage.net/green/notepage-green-efforts.htm">http://www.notepage.net/green/notepage-green-efforts.htm</a><br />
 Going Green Saves Green - <a href="http://www.notepage.net/green/green-business-tips.htm">http://www.notepage.net/green/green-business-tips.htm</a><br />
 More Green Business Tips - <a href="http://www.notepage.net/green/more-green-business-tips.htm">http://www.notepage.net/green/more-green-business-tips.htm</a><br />
 Recycling Cell Phones - <a href="http://www.notepage.net/green/recycling-cell-phones.htm">http://www.notepage.net/green/recycling-cell-phones.htm</a><br />
 Why Recycle Cell Phones - <a href="http://www.notepage.net/green/why-recycle-cell-phones.htm">http://www.notepage.net/green/why-recycle-cell-phones.htm</a><br />
<br />
<b>Twitter</b><br />
Follow NotePage on Twitter - <a href="http://twitter.com/notepage">http://twitter.com/notepage</a> or follow at @notepage <br />
<br />
<b>Thank you</b><br />
We'd like to thank you for your continued support. It is through customer support and your suggestions that we've been able to continually improve the NotePage product line.<br />
<br />
Thank you for your continued support! <br />
NotePage sales team<br />
<a href="http://www.notepage.net">http://www.notepage.net </a><br />
Leaders in Wireless Messaging Software ]]>
            </description>
            <link>http://www.notepage.net/newsletter-03-30-11.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.notepage.net/newsletter-03-30-11.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 1 Apr 2011 09:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Why You Should Recycle Cell Phones</title>
            <description>Cellular phones and other mobile devices often contain toxic materials that can pollute the environment. The chemicals contained in the cell phones and electronics are harmful to the health of both humans and animals. Cell phones and their accessories contain a large number of hazardous substances known as Persistent, Bioaccumulative, and Toxic Chemicals PBTs. Some of the chemicals contained in the PBTs have been known to cause damage to nervous systems, reproductive systems, and developmental systems, as well as causing cancer. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.notepage.net/green/why-recycle-cell-phones.htm&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; &gt;Why You Should Recycle Cell Phones&lt;/a&gt;</description>
            <link>http://www.notepage.net/green/why-recycle-cell-phones.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.notepage.net/green/why-recycle-cell-phones.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2010 09:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Cell Phone Etiquette - Part 2</title>
            <description>Cellular telephones, or &lt;i&gt;cellphones&lt;/i&gt;, are an important part of modern society. When &lt;i&gt;Miss Manners &lt;/i&gt;wrote about good manners and etiquette, mobile phones did not exist nearly to the extent they do in our society today. In an effort to assist cellphone users, we have written up some guidelines to help people use their mobile phones appropriately while navigating in polite society. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.notepage.net/learning-center/cell-phone-etiquette-part-2.htm&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; &gt;Cell Phone Etiquette - Part 2&lt;/a&gt;</description>
            <link>http://www.notepage.net/learning-center/cell-phone-etiquette-part-2.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.notepage.net/learning-center/cell-phone-etiquette-part-2.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 7 Jul 2010 09:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>NotePage Newsletter for SMS and Text Messaging</title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[Welcome to NotePage news. <br />
<br />
<b>NotePage Education Center</b><br />
In order to help customers and potential customers better understand text messaging and how to use NotePages various software applications we have compiled a number of educational resources.<br />
<br />
Check out the NotePage learning center! <a href="http://www.notepage.net/learning-center/notepage-learning-center.htm" target="_blank">http://www.notepage.net/learning-center/notepage-learning-center.htm</a><br />
<br />
<b>Video Tutorials</b><br />
We have compiled a series of video tutorials to assist customers in utilizing various PageGate and NotePager Pro features.<br />
<a href="http://www.notepage.net/video-tutorials.htm" target="_blank">http://www.notepage.net/video-tutorials.htm</a><br />
<br />
<b>New Integration Partner - Simple Server Monitor</b><br />
Simple Server Monitor is an affordable, powerful, and user-friendly server monitoring utility that will continually monitor the status of your servers and web applications. When network uptime losses are detected, our monitoring utility notifies you via any combination of these alert methods <a href="http://www.notepage.net/simple-server-monitor/simple-server-monitor.htm" target="_blank">http://www.notepage.net/simple-server-monitor/simple-server-monitor.htm</a><br />
<br />
<b>Cellular Phone Etiquette</b><br />
Todays society is all about being connected 24-7. Cell phones now provide instant access to anyone and everyone, from corporate executives to housewives and children alike. While cellular connectivity is a comfort to some, it can be rude and disruptive to others. You may wish to be available at all times, but there are some times when it is simply not appropriate to use your cell phone.<br />
<a href="http://www.notepage.net/cellular-phone-etiquette.htm" target="_blank">http://www.notepage.net/cellular-phone-etiquette.htm</a><br />
<br />
<b>Increasing Business and Personal Productivity</b><br />
Small business owners frequently juggle a variety of roles within their companies. Creating a balance and effectively managing available time is extremely important to most small businesses. In order to economize and make the most of the available time, you should implement a time management plan.<br />
<a href="http://www.small-business-software.net/increasing-productivity.htm" target="_blank">http://www.small-business-software.net/increasing-productivity.htm</a><br />
<br />
<b>Green Section on The Website</b><br />
NotePage, Inc. has instituted a company policy that details how we pledge to do our part in caring for the environment.<br />
<a href="http://www.notepage.net/green/notepage-green-company.htm" target="_blank">http://www.notepage.net/green/notepage-green-company.htm</a><br />
<br />
<b>NotePage Green Efforts</b><br />
NotePage is an eco-friendly business. In recent years, we have made a number of changes in an effort to become a more environmentally-friendly and conscientious business. Here are just a few of the things that NotePage has done in our effort to become a more <i>green</i> business...<br />
<a href="http://www.notepage.net/green/notepage-green-efforts.htm" target="_blank">http://www.notepage.net/green/notepage-green-efforts.htm</a><br />
<br />
<b>Suggested Websites</b><br />
<b></b><br />
<b>Digital Sound Effects</b><br />
Wide variety of royalty free sound effects available for download. The sound effects can even be converted into mobile ringtones.<br />
<a href="http://www.digital-sound-effects.com" target="_blank">http://www.digital-sound-effects.com</a><br />
<br />
<b>PowerPoint Templates</b><br />
Themed PowerPoint Templates for business presentations. The professional quality PowerPoint templates polish presentations.<br />
<a href="http://www.ppt-templates.net" target="_blank">http://www.ppt-templates.net</a><br />
<br />
<b>Twitter</b><br />
Follow NotePage on Twitter - http://twitter.com/notepage or follow at <a href="http://twitter.com/notepage" target="_blank">@notepage</a>]]>
            </description>
            <link>http://www.notepage.net/newsletter-01-20-10.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.notepage.net/newsletter-01-20-10.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2010 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>New SMS Learning Center Launched</title>
            <description>NotePage has recently introduced an SMS learning center to assist customers in sending text messages to mobile phones and wireless devices. The SMS and text messaging center includes interactive video tutorials, educational articles and support resources all pertinent to the sending of text and SMS messages. NotePage, Inc. has long been a leader in wireless communication and the SMS learning center expands on their commitment to educate users about messaging technologies, procedures and protocols.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The SMS learning center and videos are freely available, and no login is required. Additional details can be found at: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.notepage.net/learning-center/notepage-learning-center.htm&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; &gt;http://www.notepage.net/learning-center/notepage-learning-center.htm&lt;/a&gt;</description>
            <link>http://www.notepage.net/press-release-sms-learning-center.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.notepage.net/press-release-sms-learning-center.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2010 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>NotePage Is a Green Business</title>
            <description>A business that makes the decision to be environmentally-conscious will often promote goodwill among potential customers, while making the world a better place for future generations. Many businesses hesitate to adopt green practices because they fear it will hurt their bottom line and negatively impact profits. But many eco-conscious businesses discover that they can actually save money and bring in new customers who specifically patronize companies that actively make an effort to be environmentally friendly. Many customers may even be willing to pay a bit more for a product or service from a company that is green.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Many businesses already do things that are eco-friendly, not necessarily because they are sensitive to green living, but simply to save money. That does not, however, diminish the value of their green efforts. The trick for businesses is to be eco-friendly without compromising profitability. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.notepage.net/steps-businesses-can-take-to-go-green.htm&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; &gt;Steps Businesses Can Take to Go Green&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description>
            <link>http://www.notepage.net/steps-businesses-can-take-to-go-green.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.notepage.net/steps-businesses-can-take-to-go-green.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2009 09:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Multifunction Messaging Server Updated</title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[NotePage, Inc. is pleased to announce the release of <a href="http://www.notepage.net/pagegate.htm" target="_blank">PageGate version 5</a>. PageGate is a complete wireless messaging solution that incorporates a wide variety of messaging protocols for sending messages to mobile phones, wireless devices, fax machines and pagers. <br />
<br />
Wireless messaging communication is important in todays fast paced environment. PageGate allows critical alerts to be sent instantly to wireless devices regardless of the recipients locations. PageGate supports group messaging and preprogrammed alerts, so that with the press of a single button notification can be sent to defined groups of individuals.&nbsp;&nbsp;<br />
<br />
To ensure delivery even in the event of connectivity loss, PageGate version 5 supports failover options and redundant connectors. Messages that cannot be delivered to their intended recipients can be automatically redirected to a backup recipient or group, or the message can be sent to the same recipient via an alternative delivery method. <br />
<br />
Messages can be sent into PageGate via: a Windows client, web page, email, commandline, text file, serial port, modem, wireless modem, wireless phone or the Internet.<br />
<br />
PageGate's modular design allows users to select from eight different interfaces, allowing users to scale PageGate to meet their business needs and expand as their needs change. Interfaces can be used individually or in conjunction with each other, as PageGate can receive and process messages simultaneously from multiple sources.<br />
<br />
PageGate supports multiple telecom carriers, multiple connectors, direct connections to paging terminals, group paging, scheduled messages, repeating messages, on-call groups, and ad hoc paging, making it ideal for demanding, high-end messaging and communication. <br />
<br />
PageGate supports a variety of delivery methods including the following protocols: Fax, GSM-AT, SMTP, SNPP, TAP, Tone, UCP and WCTP. Messages can also be delivered out the serial port, or via the Internet and TCP/IP to another computer.]]>
            </description>
            <link>http://www.notepage.net/press-release-pagegate5.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.notepage.net/press-release-pagegate5.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2007 09:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>NotePage SMS and Text Messaging News</title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[Welcome to NotePage news. If preferred this newsletter can also be viewed online at: <a href="http://www.notepage.net/newsletter-051106.htm" target="blank">http://www.notepage.net/newsletter-051106.htm</a> <br>
<br>
<b>Realtors and RSS </b><br>
<b><i>Reach Customers A New Way </i></b><br>
A large number of NotePage customers are realtors so I thought I would share this article about how Realtors are using NotePage's other software to increase communication. Daily more and more Realtors are turning to RSS as a tool to market homes for sale. The growing RSS phenomenon in the realty market makes perfect sense. <br>
<br>
Unlike email RSS feeds have a 100% delivery rate. In addition the costs involved in creating and managing an RSS feed are insignificant when compared to the print advertising Realtors spend on each week. Imagine the amount spent each week to promote various properties in circulars and weekly newspapers, compared to the costs associated with updating and managing an RSS feed. <br>
<a href="http://www.feedforall.com/realtors-use-rss.htm" target="blank">http://www.feedforall.com/realtors-use-rss.htm</a><br>
<br>
<b><i>NotePager Pro and PageGate Support Tips</i></b><br>
<b><i>Carrier Consolidation </i></b><br>
Many carriers that have gone through buyouts in recent years are restructuring their SMS networks to take old terminals off-line and merge other host information. A good example of this would be USA Mobility, Arch, and Metrocall. USA Mobility bought out Arch who bought out Metrocall and, for a little while, it was a guessing game as to whose host information would actually get a message delivered to a device. Fortunately, USA Mobility has decided to start clearing things up a bit and most messages can now be delivered through their Arch hosts and terminals. <br>
<br>
<b><i>Group Loops</i></b><br>
When setting up groups, try not to loop them. Let's say we have groups 1 and 2. Group 2 is in the member list of group 1. If Group 1 is in the member list of Group 2, it's going to cause a message loop that will cause issues unlike anything I've seen. I only mention this because it's something I've run into at least four times this month. <br>
<br>
<b><i>SMTP Settings </i></b><br>
When attempting to configure SMTP based carriers and recipients, we may not have the absolute, up to date information posted on the website. If a carrier has changed their cell phone or pager domain, it may take a week or two, possibly longer, for us to find out and post the relevant changes. If a carrier's SMTP settings are in question, please contact the carrier for verification from them... and let us know about it so we can make the changes appropriate. <br>
<br>
<b><i>Zetron & PageGate</i></b><br>
PageGate software supports a direct serial connection (TAP/TAPI) to a paging terminal (i.e. Zetron). For instructions about setting up PageGate with a paging terminal, please refer to NotePage's Forum at Brief list of paging terminals at <a href="http://www.alphapagingsoftware.com/terminalmanufacturers.html" target="blank">http://www.alphapagingsoftware.com/terminalmanufacturers.html</a> <br>
<br>
<b>NotePage Blog</b><br>
Read the latest industry news on NotePage's daily cellular blog. <br>
<a href="httphttp://www.notepage.net/blog.htm" target="blank">http://www.notepage.net/blog.htm</a> or grab the feed at <a href="http://www.notepage.net/blog-feed.xml" target="blank">http://www.notepage.net/blog-feed.xml</a> . <br>
<br>
<b>Need Answers Fast?</b><br>
NotePage has worked hard to develop a comprehensive support section, with many of the carriers TAP, SNPP, WCTP and SMTP settings. The support section also includes a robust forum, conduct keyword searches to find answers to common questions in seconds.<br>
<a href="http://www.notepage.net/support.htm" target="blank">http://www.notepage.net/support.htm </a><br>
<br>
<br>
<b>Thank you</b><br>
We'd like to thank you for your continued support. It is through customer support and your suggestions that we've been able to continually improve the NotePage product line.<br>
<br>
Thank you for your continued support! <br>
NotePage sales team<br>
<br>]]>
            </description>
            <link>http://www.notepage.net/newsletter-051106.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.notepage.net/newsletter-051106.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2006 09:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Streamline Solutions uses PageGate to facilitate alarm conditions.</title>
            <description>Communications Facilities, Inc. (CFI), a Streamline Solution&apos;s customer, uses Zetron Sentrimax to monitor alarm points at a variety of communication sites, including federal agencies and wireless towers. The alarm conditions indicate a range of items from power failures to temperature alerts. &lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Streamline Solutions, LLC. was able to optimize CFI&apos;s communications and increase response times by installing PageGate with the GetSerial Interface. The added functionality of PageGate means that designated Communications Facilities, Inc. staff receive detailed text messages about each alarm condition. &lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.notepage.net/press-release-streamline.htm&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Increase Functionality for Minor Expense&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
            <link>http://www.notepage.net/press-release-streamline.htm</link>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2006 09:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>The Bat! Integrates with NotePager Pro</title>
            <description>NotePage, Inc., a leader in the wireless messaging software industry, announces software integration with RitLabs. NotePage&apos;s NotePager Pro, text messaging software now integrates with RITlab&apos;s The Bat!, email client software. Using NotePager Pro in conjunction with The Bat! allows users to receive critical email alerts on their mobile devices that come into their email mailbox.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Using filters within The Bat! users define parameters, that determine which messages should be passed to NotePager Pro. NotePager Pro then quickly sends the contents of the email message to the designated cell phone or pager. &lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Users no longer have to sit at their computer waiting for urgent emails. They can work remotely while still having the ability to quickly respond to critical issues received via email. Using NotePager Pro and TheBat! users can now receive alerts on a large variety of pagers, SMS phones, and other devices.&lt;br&gt;</description>
            <link>http://www.notepage.net/the-bat-integration-press.htm</link>
            <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2005 09:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AT&amp;T Uses NotePage&apos;s Technology to Assist Blood Centers</title>
            <description>AT&amp;T Wireless is funding a text-messaging pilot for six months to help the Blood Center target type O blood donors - a blood type that is in the greatest demand. Type O blood is considered the &quot;universal donor&quot; and can be transfused into any patient in an emergency.</description>
            <link>http://www.notepage.net/press-puget-sound.htm</link>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2004 08:05:43 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Kiwi Syslog Daemon monitors networks and NotePager Pro sends alerts to cell phones and pagers about system problems.</title>
            <description>- NotePage, Inc., a leader in the wireless messaging software industry, announces software integration with Kiwi Enterprises. NotePage&apos;s NotePager Pro, text messaging software, integrates with Kiwi Enterprises&apos; Kiwi Syslog Daemon, network management software. Using NotePager Pro in combination with Kiwi Syslog adds another level of notification to network management.</description>
            <link>http://www.notepage.net/kiwi-syslog/pressannouncements.htm</link>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2004 21:37:24 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>PageGate Integrates With Orion Network Performance Monitor</title>
            <description>Receive instant alerts on pagers and cell phones about network status.</description>
            <link>http://www.notepage.net/press-solarwinds-press.htm</link>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Personal Stock Monitor Gold Integrates with NotePager Pro</title>
            <description>DTLink Software is pleased to announce the immediate availability of Personal Stock Monitor Gold 5.2, a live stock ticker tape, multi-currency portfolio manager and advanced research assistant for individual investors.</description>
            <link>http://www.notepage.net/press-personal-stock-monitor.htm</link>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>NotePager Pro Nominated for the 2003 Shareware Industry Awards &quot;Best Business Application or Utility&quot;</title>
            <description>NotePager Pro leverages the power of the Internet to send text messages to mobile phones and pagers.</description>
            <link>http://www.notepage.net/press-notepagerpro-nomination.htm</link>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Send SMS Anywere, Anytime to Anyone</title>
            <description>NotePager Pro leverages the power of the Internet to send SMS and text messages to mobile phones and pagers. NotePager Pro is carrier and device independent. This means it will send to any carrier, phone, pager or wireless enabled PIM. In a cost saving measure, many telecom carriers are expanding their use of the Internet as a means of accepting messages. NotePager Pro takes advantage of these new capabilities by supporting all of the latest Internet messaging protocols: SNPP, WCTP, and SMTP.</description>
            <link>http://www.notepage.net/press-send-sms-anywhere.htm</link>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Wireless Gateway Now Uses the Internet</title>
            <description>PageGate is a complete text and SMS messaging solution that incorporates the latest protocols for sending messages via the Internet to pagers, mobile phones and other wireless devices. By using the Internet as a means of accepting messages, wireless carriers are now able to save significant telecommunication charges. PageGate takes advantage of these new capabilities by supporting all the latest Internet messaging protocols: SNPP, WCTP, and SMTP.</description>
            <link>http://www.notepage.net/press-internet.htm</link>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Know When You Are Losing Money! Instant Notification of Web Failure</title>
            <description>The combined Internet Services Monitor and NotePager Pro solution monitors multiple servers on the web and notifies system administrators of any critical failures. Administrators can now respond immediately, correcting any problems, minimizing and preventing any down time. As reliance on the Internet grows, administrators now can be immediately aware of any system failures.</description>
            <link>http://www.notepage.net/press-ism.htm</link>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Reaching Out to Carriers</title>
            <description>NotePage, Inc. a leading provider of alphanumeric paging and wireless messaging software solutions, is reaching out to paging and cellular providers through a new innovative program. Carriers and wireless resellers have long struggled with how to provide a complete solution, without incurring support expenses. Through a new program designed specifically for paging carriers, NotePage may have found just the solution.</description>
            <link>http://www.notepage.net/press-special-download.htm</link>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Trigger SMS Messages From Business And Data Events</title>
            <description>Instead of you sitting in front of a computer screen waiting for something to happen, your computer can now send SMS messages to mobile phones or pagers in response to business or data eventsThis helps you react to market changes at Internet speed, saving you time and money and helping you fulfil service level obligations (and frees you from sitting at a desk).</description>
            <link>http://www.notepage.net/press-textpipe-integration.htm</link>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Paging Package Does It All!</title>
            <description>NotePage, Inc. has introduced NotePager Pro version 2, a full featured paging application for Windows that sends individual, group, pre-programmed, and scheduled messages to pagers, mobile phones, and other wireless devices.</description>
            <link>http://www.notepage.net/press-paging-package.htm</link>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Paging Package Does It All!</title>
            <description>NotePage, Inc. has released WebGate version 3.6, an easy-to-use Windows paging program that lets your PC communicate with alphanumeric and numeric pagers, PCS and digital phones, PCMCIA pager cards, billboards, and other wireless messaging devices. Using the simplest web page and e-mail technology, WebGate makes it easy to communicate with your employees and colleagues on their pagers and other wireless devices.</description>
            <link>http://www.notepage.net/presswebgate.htm</link>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
